[{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980175378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5344,"timeElapsed":25740},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980182021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6640,"timeElapsed":32384},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980184889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2866,"timeElapsed":35252},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980187924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3033,"timeElapsed":38287},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":193665,"timeElapsed":231947},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3337,"timeElapsed":235286},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6528,"timeElapsed":241817},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":27616,"timeElapsed":269435},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2553,"timeElapsed":271990},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3564,"timeElapsed":276661},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2260,"timeElapsed":278923},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1993,"timeElapsed":280917},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1963,"timeElapsed":282883},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1262,"timeElapsed":284147},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3301,"timeElapsed":287451},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442506,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5417,"timeElapsed":292869},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1754,"timeElapsed":294625},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2395,"timeElapsed":297022},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2086,"timeElapsed":299110},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":14961,"timeElapsed":315521},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4446,"timeElapsed":319968},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":9285,"timeElapsed":329255},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":9490,"timeElapsed":338747},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2470,"timeElapsed":341218},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6156,"timeElapsed":347375},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2743,"timeElapsed":350120},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980506196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6438,"timeElapsed":356559},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4238,"timeElapsed":360799},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980515843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4226,"timeElapsed":366206},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2950,"timeElapsed":369158},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3562,"timeElapsed":372722},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":18186,"timeElapsed":390909},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2590,"timeElapsed":393501},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2319,"timeElapsed":395822},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2136,"timeElapsed":397959},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":43730,"timeElapsed":441690},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980623268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":31941,"timeElapsed":473631},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":10844,"timeElapsed":493037},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1944,"timeElapsed":494983},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2520,"timeElapsed":497505},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7315,"timeElapsed":504821},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2537,"timeElapsed":507360},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9216,"timeElapsed":516577},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3208,"timeElapsed":519787},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2049,"timeElapsed":521838},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":523819},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10214,"timeElapsed":535032},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2344,"timeElapsed":537378},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2291,"timeElapsed":539670},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2018,"timeElapsed":541690},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1613,"timeElapsed":543305},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1753,"timeElapsed":545059},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2000,"timeElapsed":547061},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4123,"timeElapsed":551185},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":39275,"timeElapsed":590461},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":593688},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2153,"timeElapsed":595843},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980759041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":13443,"timeElapsed":609404},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9344,"timeElapsed":618749},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":40502,"timeElapsed":659252},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980810459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1569,"timeElapsed":660822},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":662672},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2520,"timeElapsed":665194},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1684,"timeElapsed":666879},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7550,"timeElapsed":675391},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980826204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1175,"timeElapsed":676567},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1863,"timeElapsed":678432},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":681678},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836968,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5651,"timeElapsed":687331},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1627,"timeElapsed":688959},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980946708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":108112,"timeElapsed":797071},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3317,"timeElapsed":800389},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":26802,"timeElapsed":827193},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1719,"timeElapsed":828914},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980987243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7561,"timeElapsed":837606},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7088,"timeElapsed":844696},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2603,"timeElapsed":847300},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980998314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1375,"timeElapsed":848677},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980999958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1642,"timeElapsed":850321},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":853339},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981006044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3067,"timeElapsed":856407},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981007366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1320,"timeElapsed":857729},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981009498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":859860},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981013491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2971,"timeElapsed":863853},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981015783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2290,"timeElapsed":866145},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981019026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3242,"timeElapsed":869389},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981023377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4349,"timeElapsed":873740},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981025366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1988,"timeElapsed":875729},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981027080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1712,"timeElapsed":877443},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981029112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2030,"timeElapsed":879475},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981031360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2246,"timeElapsed":881723},{"subjectID":"h1hbbj359g","prolificID":"63fbd3e8b4865c6e1fb04614","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22d246709d0172ba48f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981033360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1998,"timeElapsed":883723}]